<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<doc>
  <remarks name="MsgPack.Unpacker">
    <see cref="Unpacker"/> implements three mode, that is 'Streaming', 'Skipping' and 'Subtree'.
    <list type="bullet">
      <item>
        <para>
          <strong>Streaming</strong>
        </para>
        <para>
          When the <see cref="Read"/> is called, unpacker go into 'Streaming' mode.
          In this mode, unpacker unpacks individual entries as <see cref="MessagePackObject"/> via <see cref="Data"/> property.
          If the underlying stream is ended unexpectedly, then <see cref="Read"/> returns <c>false</c>, and <see cref="Data"/> will be <c>null</c>.
          Note that if the underlying stream is feeded, that is the <see cref="P:Stream.Length"/> is expanded and its <see cref="P:Stream.Position"/> is not forwarded,
          subsequent <see cref="Read"/> invocation will success, and <see cref="Data"/> is set as complete entry which reflects feeded binary.
        </para>
        <para>
          If the reading of the entry is completed, that is the <see cref="Data"/> is not <c>null</c>, unpacker can transit other mode.
        </para>
      </item>
      <item>
        <para>
          <strong>Skipping</strong>
        </para>
        <para>
          When the <see cref="Skip"/> is called, unpacker go into 'Skipping' mode.
          In this mode, unpacker scans the subtree where the root is current item, then returns skipped byte length.
          If the underlying stream is ended unexpectedly, it returns <c>null</c>.
          Note that if the underlying stream is feeded, that is the <see cref="P:Stream.Length"/> is expanded and its <see cref="P:Stream.Position"/> is not forwarded,
          subsequent <see cref="Skip"/> invocation will success, and returns length as complete entry which reflects feeded binary.
          <note>
            If the underlying <see cref="Stream"/> is cannot be seeked (that is, <see cref="P:Stream.CanSeek"/> is <c>false</c>),
            DO NOT use this method.
            You can buffering the content via <see cref="MemoryStream"/> instead, for example.
          </note>
        </para>
        <para>
          If the skipping of the subtree is completed, that is the return value is not <c>null</c>, unpacker can transit other mode.
        </para>
      </item>
      <item>
        <para>
          <strong>Subtree</strong>
        </para>
        <para>
          When the <see cref="ReadSubtree"/> is called, unpacker go into 'Subtree' mode.
          In this mode, any operation for this unpacker instance is invalid.
          Instead of use this instance itself, you can use subtree unpacker returned from <see cref="ReadSubtree"/>.
          The subtree unpacker is the instance which scope is limited to the subtree where the root is the current entry when <see cref="ReadSubtree"/> is called.
          The subtree unpacker also have its own mode and state.
          <note>
            <see cref="Dispose()"/> of the subtree unpacker must be called to indicate subtree unpacking is gracefully completed.
            When the extra entries are remained in the subtree, these will be skipped on the disposal process.
          </note>
        </para>
        <para>
          Once the subtree unpacking is completed gracefully, that is, <see cref="Dispose()"/> on the subtree unpacker called, the parant unpacker can transit other mode.
        </para>
      </item>
    </list>
  </remarks>
</doc>